<resources>
    <string name="app_name">supermarket_checkout</string>

    <string name="doritos">Introducing new Doritos®️ Flamin’ Hot Cool Ranch®️ Flavored Tortilla Chips, an all-new mash-up that combines the classic Cool Ranch flavor fans love with a spicy, bold crunch.

</string>


    <string name="burger">
The Halwani Bros Beef Burger is incredibly tasty and delicious.

The tender and chewy meat coupled with other condiments make it a very filling meal.

Perfect to share with family and friends.

Its great in taste.

</string>


    <string name="checken">The Qualiko Whole Chicken is your ideal choice for when you are hosting a family dinner or having friends over for a party. It is a Halal chicken and can be used in cooking varieties of dishes like curries, soups and rice.</string>


    <string name="chepsi">شيبسي عملك طعمين جداد من كنتاكي أوريجينال و زنجر !
طعم كان لازم يحصل !</string>


    <string name="dairymilk">Crack open a yummy block to release the sweet nut crunch.
 </string>


    <string name="gebna">Have a rejuvenating and enriching experience with the President Feta Cheese. Its soft and creamy texture perfectly melts into your mouth for a tantalizing feel.
</string>

    <string name="meraba">Enjoy the taste of fresh fruits with Vitrac Strawberry Cream Jam.

You can prepare a delicious sandwich with creamy Vitrac jam with fresh strawberry flavor.

Vitrac’s creamy strawberry jam is rich with pureed fruit.

Its creamy texture gives a smooth natural fruit taste that is easy to spread, perfect for desserts and quick sandwiches.</string>

    <string name="president3">Enjoy an intense snacking experience with the President triangle cheese.

This cheese offers a rich flavor to satisfy your taste buds.

It is pre-cut in triangular, bite-sized pieces for convenient snacking.

You can consume this cheese by itself or even add as a topping to various foods like pizzas, pasta, crackers and toasts.

It ranks high in nutrients and is sure to provide you optimal nourishment.</string>

    <string name="zabady">
        Almarai Treats Strawberry Tart Yogurt - 100 gm

    </string>
</resources>